OK.
Caviar, you can start recording.
I have something.
Yeah, OK.
Regarding that ABC changes that Naria has
discussed in that call all,
all the changes that are in that are done
in the ABC folder I think according to
the domain wise like clients domain and
contract domain.
So those changes have already been done
by the other team.
So what we have to do in our case is that
we have to do few changes at two places
like at this level here in input fields
we need to add these two these two
parameters.
So here by click on this clicking on this
plus button we can add these two
parameters and we have to make sure that
we need to check here in this check box
because these are necessary components.
And what are the other things that we
need to do here is that is source batch
ID,
source execution run ID and source batch
entertain.
These 3 has to be unchecked because in
place of these three parameters,
we need to add these two parameters.
And other thing is that and here job
preload also here in input fields,
we need to map the incoming fields with
that field.
Like these two parameters are actually I
can see these two parameters they're
coming from this subtask flow, I think.
So whenever we open any task flow,
we can see these two parameters that are
being already added or or they are coming
from the input fields.
I can.
So for these input fields we need to map
the in batch ID by clicking here earlier
it will be something like content but we
need to change here to field and then we
need to map the whatever the input
parameter that is coming from that start
input fields.
So we need to map it here like this.
These are actually done so only at these
two places only a job level we need to do
the changes.
And one more thing is like here you can
see in input fields there is some batch
and ID that I have given right?
So this can be fetched from batch and
sourcing stats table.
So,
which is a new table that is introduced
for this new ABC changes so.
This is the batch sourcing stats table
that they have introduced to include
source batch IDs also.
So like even for this table we'll have to
make the metadata increase right?
This table we can make entry only once OK
but means what they said is that I was
for CRC or batch ID.
Target batch ID is 455 and source batch
ID is 151 right?
So we need to make entry only once for
this CRC batch.
So here on Friday have entered the record
for our batch ID,
CERC batch ID 455 and our source batch ID
is 151.
Till now I think we have one source and
only I guess.
Am I correct?
Yes so so for that I have inserted 1
record.
This is one time entry only.
So this is the batch ID of target batch
ID,
source batch ID and execution run IDs
coming from batch run stats table.
And also this batch run ID is also coming
from batch run stats table for this batch
ID.
And this is a auto increment column.
So no need to insert any value into this
column.
It will be automatically populated
whenever we insert a record and source
batch execution run ID means for this 151
source batch ID right,
we'll get one execution ID.
So that will be inserted here in this
column and sourcing start time sourcing
and time on that day we have populated
these columns as which is starting from
1900 year to till the date.
I mean the day we have inserted record
right.
So on on that day,
we have given this as 31st August.
So these are the two time stamps that we
need to queue and what Ria has said that
is that the sourcing window time stamps
will be coming from this table only.
So whatever the time stamps will be there
here for ATL data ingestion table,
it will pick the those time stamps
starting time and ending time and these
are the audit columns.
This is the record that we have inserted
for the CERC.
So here you can see this batch run ID
right?
So this batch run ID is given in start
input fields here.
This is the one I have given that value
here.
So for the all other task flows on the
tables that you are working,
you can include these two parameters and
this value that's it.
And here this is 11 place and other
places that just we need to map these two
columns already we can see whenever you
open the task flow or this subtask
preload component.
So here we can see these two that
parameters that are coming in.
We just need to map those two columns
here by clicking on the field in dropdown
we can click on that field button and
after that we need to pick up the the
parameter.
Can you like also share them like
metadata entry sheet like which you used
to make entries here in this table for
the new table Batch sourcing SAT table OK
this this is the only table we have to
make an entry right?
Only one time entry is fine.
Already we have insert.
This is for like different asset we are
working.
So if you could share.
OK, OK, fine.
You can one second.
Yeah, I'll check this and I'll share.
I have insert query somewhere.
Yeah, Kavya, I'll share.
It was somewhere in these tabs.
So is that clear or so these are the only
changes we are making, right?
Yeah,
at these two places only are for job
level already domain level changes that
they are done by other team.
OK.
So in ABC folders in our clients domain,
we can see the changes that they are done
only for job level only.
We need to do these changes in those two
places like you are getting batch ID from
source bat batch stats, right?
We're copying the batch IDs I have taken
from batch run stats.
OK,
like currently what from where we have to
copy from source batch run stats like you.
How in inside then we call actually.
Yeah,
actually in this sourcing stats table we
need to enter only once for our assets.
So as our asset is CRC, right.
So for CRC we have a target batch ID as
455 and source batch ID is 151 and we are
having only one source I think till now.
Yeah.
So I have taken that 455 batch ID from
the batch run stats table and have copied
batch run ID and batch execution ID all
from batch run stats table.
OK.
You copied from batch run like you have
inserted into batch sourcing stats, right?
Yes.
From that batch sourcing stats you have
copied into the job task flow, right?
Yeah, yeah, batch run ID.
Oh,
it would be same same for every task flow,
right?
Every task flow, every, every,
every asset, CRC asset, Yeah,
whatever that whatever the task flows or
the tables that you are working.
So here in input fields,
what is the value?
Whatever the value that you will see here,
right This one yeah,
batch ID this will be same.
So can you share that in the group or
personally to No, no, no,
you can you can copy you can copy take
this as a reference claim payment record,
claim payment record.
You can take this task as a reference and
you can copy it here.
OK,
here batch type what you're taking batch
type, actually batch type,
what RIA had said is that here we need to
give data share if we are working on that
data share, OK.
But here we are not.
I mean the source is not data share,
right In CRC.
That's why I haven't given any value.
But this is the value that I have taken
from batch sourcing stats table, batch ID,
sourcing stats table,
batch sourcing stats table, batch run ID.
This is the batch run.
OK Batch sourcing stats table.
OK.
You can copy by taking this as different.
OK.
OK, Everybody's clear with that.
Or if you had a,
if you're having any doubts, ask me.
Yeah, Jayshree.
OK, fine.